scitraining.com 2019-03-06

# Privacy Policy - Stratford Career Institute

_March 29, 2018_   

We value and understand the importance of privacy for all our web visitors. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Stratford Career Institute and its websites. This policy is used to describe the types of information Stratford (herein referred to as “we” and “our”) collect from website visitors (herein referred to as “you(r)” and “user(s),” and how we use and store that information. Any time you view and use our websites, you accept this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy demonstrates our commitment to your privacy in the following ways: 

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site   
2\. The organization collecting the information   
3\. How the information is used   
4\. With whom the information may be shared   
5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information   
6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Stratford’s control   
7\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you can contact us at [contact@scitraining.com](mailto:contact@scitraining.com). 

**  
Information Collection and Use**

Stratford Career Institute is the sole owner of the information collected when a student or prospective student contacts us. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Stratford collects information from our students and visitors in several ways.   
**  
They include: 

1\. Request for Information 

**Prospective students will ask for detailed information about our programs. This may be done by telephone, and/or by filling out a form - either paper-based or on our website - where the user is required to provide personal information that generally includes name, address, phone, and email address. This information is used to contact the user about the course for which they have expressed interest. We may ask for demographic information such as gender and age, to personalize our correspondence, or to distinguish adults from minors. **

2\. Enroll Online 

**We request information from new students on our Internet enrollment form. Here, a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for correspondence, billing purposes, and to ship textbooks. If we have trouble processing a shipment or payment, this information is used to get in touch with the user. **

3\. Cookies for eService, our online Student Center 

**A cookie is a piece of data stored on an individual's computer that contains information about the user. Stratford uses temporary cookies to verify that a registered student has correctly logged into our online student center, eService. Once the user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates. If a user selects the “Remember Me” option, a permanent cookie is created on the user’s system. This cookie contains only an encrypted student number and no other information. If a user rejects a cookie, they may still use our site, but will not be able to take advantage of our e-Service options. **

4\. Cookies/Pixels for Ads 

**Stratford also uses a temporary cookie to record visitors who arrive on our site in response to advertisements. Third party vendors, including Google, show ads for our websites on the Internet. Sometimes, these third party vendors, including Google, also use cookies or pixels to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. No personally identifiable information is stored and the cookies terminate after 30-90 days. Users may also opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page: [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).   
**  
4\. Log Files   
**We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. **

Sharing of Personal Information 

**We do not sell, rent, or lease email addresses to any third parties.   
We will not disclose your credit card number or other personal information, except as necessary to collect payment.   
We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

Stratford Career Institute uses the information you provide us to improve our services to you and to tell you about new products and services that may be of interest to you. From time to time, we may also share personal contact information and demographic information about or students and prospective students with reliable select business partners, such as advertisers and other third parties. 

We will not disclose your academic record, or grades except as required by law, or at your personal request. **

Links 

**Our websites may contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Stratford Career Institute is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

**Refer a Friend**   
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name, mailing address and email address. Stratford Career Institute will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to visit the site. We may also use this information to send a follow-up mailing by surface mail. The friend may contact Stratford Career Institute at [admissions@scitraining.com](mailto:admissions@scitraining.com) or call 1-800-435-5338 to request the removal of this information from our database at any time. 

**Security & Information Storage**   
This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, all information is protected both online and offline. 

Any personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information we collect from students is securely stored in accordance with the law. 

Any personally identifiable information collected on our websites is encrypted using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology. This assures the user that no one can see your private information except for you and Stratford Career Institute. To learn more about SSL, follow this link: <https://www.verisign.com/site/ssl.html>. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information offline. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a student services representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers where we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment, behind locked doors. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [admissions@scitraining.com](mailto:contact@scitraining.com).   
**  
Registration Verification**   
Students who register for our online student center, e-Service are sent a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established students will also receive confirmation of examination results, or other communications by email. As a security precaution and to protect the privacy of our students, if an outbound email is returned to us due to an invalid email address, we will suspend e-servicing privileges for that account instantly. If you suspect that your account with the school has been suspended, you may contact [instruct@scitraining.com](mailto:instruct@scitraining.com) to have your Internet servicing account reinstated. 

**Correcting/Updating Personal Information**   
If a student’s personal information changes, we provide a way to correct, update or remove that personal data. This can be done by contacting Stratford at 1-800-435-5338, using our online student center, eService, or by emailing us at [instruct@scitraining.com](mailto:instruct@scitraining.com). 

**Children & Minors**   
Stratford’s websites are open to Internet users of all ages. Please note, however, that our products are meant for adults age 18 and older. Any individual under the age of 18 must obtain the written signature of a parent or legal guardian in order to enroll in a Stratford course and therefore cannot enroll online. 

**Choice/Opt-out**   
Our students and prospective students are given notification of ‘opting-in’ to our mailing lists at the time they request information about a Stratford program. Individuals can ‘opt-out’ of any mailing list (email and/or postal mail) at any time by emailing us at [admissions@scitraining.com or calling 1-800-254-4070. Users may also opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the ](mailto:admissions@scitraining.com)

[_Google advertising opt-out page_](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/). 

**Notification of Changes**   
This Privacy Policy may be updated or modified at any time. Please refer to the date at the top of this page to see when the most recent change was made.
